(Mike:)Hey, Froot Loops,
wanna hit your fan switch?
(Howard:)Check.
(Cosmonaut:)He calls you Froot Loops
because of your very gay haircut?
No, it's because I live with my mom
and she makes me Froot Loops.
(Cosmonaut:)Go with gay story.
People are more accepting of that.
(Mike:)Actually, Froot Loops
just got married to a girl.
(Cosmonaut:)Congratulations.
(Howard:)Thanks.
We decided to do it before the launch.
(Cosmonaut:)You and Mrs. Loops
have a big wedding?
(Howard:)Not exactly.
(Howard:)Listen, if you don't mind,
I'm not really up for chatting.
I'm just gonna sit here quietly
and let my life flash before my eyes.
(Howard:)That went really quick.
Let me try it again.
(Howard:)Close your eyes. Put out your hand.
l got you something special.